<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" version="5.0" xml:lang="en-US">
  <info>
    <title>???</title>
    <date remap="dcterms.created">2023-12-18T16:12:23Z</date>
    <date remap="dcterms.modified">2023-12-19T09:44:17Z</date>
  </info>
  <chapter>
    <title/>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Aaron's Portfolio: A Showcase of Literary and Technical Know-how</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para>All articles are previously published and owned by the author.</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Note to the Reader</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para>Howdy,</para>
    <para>Thanks for reading my portfolio. All works herein were written  using Linux. Linux is my daily driver. I truly believe in free and open  source software. Getting that out of the way, my goal is to  demonstrate my ability to structure data  through technology, using LaTeX, DITA, ASCIIDOC. Markdown, ReStructure or DocBook, as well as showoff my knack for the written word.  This document was written in DocBook, but I’ve used all of the above XML  formats for previous projects. I like DITA the best, there’s something  esoteric about it. However, LaTeX is great for accessibility.  I’m genuinely fascinated by the way that data is structured.  Both good literature and technical manuals have great structure. Moreover, The articles in this document tend to be on the shorter side, for longer articles, go <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QYyHK9fd1jtglAVnwC386e_C_PdT_wKr/view">here</link>. Also,  for samples of my technical documentation skills, checkout <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://www.fileago.com/docs">FileAgo</link>. </para>
    <para>I’ll let you in on a secret, a secret that some have held against me but I think is a net positive, I’m not in love with technology, sure, I’ve learned to love it, I can even teach others to use it, but at heart I’m a writer. My journey into the digital domain began with a love of  Kurt Vonnegut’s novels and continues with writing technical documents for  file sharing technology written in Golang. In the end, I feel this makes  me a stronger writer, I could scribble onto stone tablets or use a  typewriter. It’s the craft of writing, the power of the written word  and the structure of content that interests me, whether technology or  an old-timey typewriter is used to arrive at a well crafted narrative  doesn’t matter to me, as long as we get there. Let’s agree to do it on  Linux and forego the typewriter; ink is too expensive  these days.</para>
    <para>To answer any question, no I will not participate any testing or unpaid sample writings. My portfolio represents thousands of hours of  research, editing, planning and designing.</para>
    <para>Best regards,</para>
    <para>Aaron Feldsteen</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Traces of the King of Kowloon</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para><emphasis role="underline">DISCLAIMER</emphasis>: Articles may have been published in regions where English  Creole is spoken such as India or the Ukraine. All articles are  printed as emended by the Editor. My goal is to demonstrate my ability  to write for all audiences. This includes projects for Indian and  </para>
    <para>            Eastern European consumers who speak their own unique blend of English  and their mother tongue. If You have a question about any particular  wording, contact me.</para>
    <para>Editorial</para>
    <para>He might've been crazy. His family disowned him, stating that he was mentally unbalanced and a public nuisance. To make matters worse, his wife grew tired and left him for his obsessive scribbling on walls and  lunacy. Who was he? Tsang Tsou Choi was disputably the King of Hong Kong and undoubtedly a prolific graffiti artist. Nowadays, due to the march of time and politics most of his oeuvre is nothing more than an artifact of memory. Thankfully, the legend of this mad genius lives on.&lt;</para>
    <para>Interestingly, a Hong Kong magazine named him one of the city's ten least influential people in 2017, an unsung underdog. Yet, his graffiti has inspired fashion designers, art directors, interior decorators and CD  cover artists alike. He has inspired innovative artists like also Oscar Ho. And unlike most artists, Tsang Tsou Choi had his 15 minutes of fame before shuffling off this mortal coil, he appeared in a commercial for Swipe Cleaner, in the ad he wiped away his permanent ink graffiti, proclaiming the product's effectiveness  to Hong Kong's consumers.</para>
    <para> At the height of his graffiti career, Tsang Tsou Choi's territorial markings were an ever-present aspect of the streets of Hong Kong. They could be seen on utility boxes, pillars, pavements, street furniture, walls, and even the occasional car. More than art, these scribbling on the wall were territorial <emphasis>pissings</emphasis>, claiming ownership of Hong Kong's Wedding Card Street and various other localities.</para>
    <para>During 2016, when more of his work remained, I saw his graffiti on the Star Ferry Terminal. As well as a few pieces on the sidewalk. Luckily, the Star Ferry Terminal piece, with its overlapping characters, is now protected by Hong Kong's government with an acrylic overlay, but much of his work, due to pro-Beijing sentiment  and modernization has suffered erasure. Even his protected works have been vandalized and restored many times.</para>
    <para>Here or gone, too many, viewing his work would be as exciting as seeing Dan Flavin's singular neon bulb installation, but to appreciate it, one must understand the beauty of Chinese characters, when written out  they are cosmological, and the suffering of those who've lost their homestead. As a Jew, I relate to Tsang  Tsou Choi's plight. I feel we've been marginalized and forced to live as strangers among strange lands.There's a parallel between our lives; Judea became Palestine and Hong Kong China. And so, I feel a connection to this allegedly lunatic artist.</para>
    <para>Politics aside, these markings of turf usually declare Tsang Tsou Choi's title, Emperor or King of Kowloon, his family tree (a variable list of about 20 individuals), the names of illustrious emperors along with the exclamation "Down with the Queen of England!" Like most, I have to ask is Choi who he claims to be? It's unknown if he ever took a DNA test, and even if he did, the DNA of ancient emperors of Hong Kong isn't just laying around in jars. Perhaps there are samples of despot DNA in ancient amphora, a lock of hair or the like, somewhere, but I don't care if Choi is the rightful heir of Hong Kong or just a crazed street artist, I like him, he's got hutzpah.</para>
    <para>His work isn’t  just a madman writing a manifesto on the walls of Hong Kong, his work has evolved.</para>
    <para>In Choi’s earlier works, cries to right the misappropriation of his land weren't always so formulaic. He sometimes included excerpts from ancient texts and various other maxims. Best of all, he occasionally demanded that the government pay him land taxes. There's an irony in this, we all pay taxes and die - this artist demanded to be paid taxes in retribution and, as long as his works remain, is immortal, but I'm stating  the obvious. Thinking about it all, perhaps Choi isn’t merely a lunatic. He’s an artist who found a formula and medium for an unusual narrative. </para>
    <para>It's said that his graffiti not only demonstrates his continual obsession of stating a claim of rightful</para>
    <para>ownership over Kowloon but also a boundless and relentless transformation of Hong Kong into an urban canvas, whether the ladder is for better or worse, I can't say. I can say that Hong Kong has more skyscrapers than Buddhist temples. This modern landscape has been marked by Banksy and other artist who followed in Tsang Tsou Choi's footsteps. Theses artists, like Choi, tagged this odd world of junk boats (which still do exist in the harbor),  skyscrapers, and turmoil.</para>
    <para>As far as I know, Tsang Tsou Choi's works were last documented on January 16, 2015 At the time, only six adorned the streets of Hong Kong. And regrettably, On April 23rd 2021, one of the king of Kowloon’s pieces on the Kwun Tong bridge was again vandalized, allegedly by pro-Beijing supporters. Choi died on the 15 of July 2007 of a heart attack, not knowing that most of his legacy would be destroyed by modernization and angry tourists from the PRC. He was 85 at the time of passing and his last wish, another exhibition. To this day, Choi’s pedigree remains a mystery, yet, he is an artistic legend and inspiration for many. </para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold"> Excerpt from How to be a Great Product Manager with Nino Tasco</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para><emphasis role="underline">DISCLAIMER</emphasis>: Articles may have been published in regions where English  Creole is spoken such as India or the Ukraine. All articles are  printed as emended by the Editor. My goal is to demonstrate my ability  to write for all audiences. This includes projects for Indian and  </para>
    <para>            Eastern European consumers who speak their own unique blend of English  and their mother tongue. If You have a question about any particular  wording, contact me.</para>
    <para>Interview</para>
    <para>What makes a great Product Manager?</para>
    <para>There are two qualities I look for in a Product Manager: curiosity and the ability to work within a framework. </para>
    <para>In fact, whenever I interview potential Product Managers, I want to see how curious they are. [I want to know] their hobbies and the questions they ask. As for working within a framework, I like to see Product Managers that can actually apply a discipline to a product.</para>
    <para>Most of all, I don't want PMs [to] think "I have a great idea, the end product will arrive in a bolt of lightning." That [may] happen once, but it isn’t repeatable. So, when I hire Product Managers, I'm looking for [those who] have a framework, and that can deliver repeatable results by going back to that framework over and over again.</para>
    <para>Can you learn to be a great Product Manager?</para>
    <para>Product Management can be learned, it’s a discipline. At the end of the day, it's a series of tasks. Think about these tasks as problem statements. And in fact, sometimes you have to fight your instincts to go [and] do what you think is best.</para>
    <para>I've learned (through both hard and easy means) that instincts aren't always what makes a great product. Discipline is what makes a great product. Correct methodologies, disciplines, frameworks, all of those put together, whatever term you want to use — can be learned and when applied, they forge great Product Managers.</para>
    <para>Product Managers can come from any background. I've seen great Product Managers that were startup founders, former Engineers, and those without any technical background.</para>
    <para>Product Managers who are interested in tech, even if their tech roots are not as strong, have a different angle of going at it, and can provide value.</para>
    <para>Thinking about it, startup founders make great Product Managers because they had to solve every problem in their organization, and so they understand the role of Product Management. Former Engineers, like myself, are fit for this role because they are curious, always asking “why, why, why?”</para>
    <para>If you're debating between Product Management and Project Management, I feel it comes down to one thing: how curious are you?</para>
    <para>Are some languages harder to work with?</para>
    <para>There are languages that present unique challenges, for sure. In languages like Hindi, speakers often use English-borrowed words, we call it “Hinglish.” Or, the User may speak in a combination of or Punjabi, Hindi, and English. In languages like Korean, the concept of words are much more fluid than they are in English.</para>
    <para>Each language has its own little twist that needs to be solved. To compensate for these twists, Google’s quality metrics are based on word-error rate: if you said 100 words, how many words did Google understand?</para>
    <para>There are two sides to Google Speech: on one hand — there’s TTS or Text To Speech, and on the other hand — there’s speech to text, called ASR (Automatic Speech Recognition). During ASR, audio files are translated to words that a computer can understand.</para>
    <para>But, if a computer wants to respond to you, it must synthesize text into an audio file that can be played back, and this process is somewhat complex.</para>
    <para>For example, there's speech to text and then there’s text to meaning, something we call Natural Language Understanding (NLU). Natural language Understanding is a different team. The Fulfillment Team is also involved in with Speech, they pull information from different databases [to answer the questions from User to Google].</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Inshore Fishing Cocoa Beach </emphasis>
    </para>
    <para><emphasis role="underline">DISCLAIMER</emphasis>: Articles may have been published in regions where English  Creole is spoken such as India or the Ukraine. All articles are  printed as emended by the Editor. My goal is to demonstrate my ability  to write for all audiences. This includes projects for Indian and  </para>
    <para>            Eastern European consumers who speak their own unique blend of English  and their mother tongue. If You have a question about any particular  wording, contact me.</para>
    <para>Informative</para>
    <para>Cocoa Beach is referred to as the “Surfing Capital of the East Coast” because of the region’s choppy waters. The white-cresting waves attract surfers and anglers alike. There’s no doubt about it, there’s big fish below the turbulent seas. In fact, Cocoa Beach’s waters are abundant with Tarpon and Pompano. During the warm Summer months, you may even sight one of the region’s infamous Blacktip or Bull shark. Moreover, Cocoa Beach is renowned for possessing soft gray sand beaches. The soft sand beckons barefoot wade fishing or Fly Fishing along the shore.</para>
    <para>Cocoa Beach’s variety of sea life is exceptional. Expect to reel-in a myriad of fish while wading the crystal clear waters. One angler, in the pages of Floridatoday.com, reported hooking 100 different species of fish during a single expedition. Although this tale is much too reminiscent of Hemingway’s Santiago and his Marlin, the region is known for a variety of fauna along the shoreline.</para>
    <para>Expect to reel-in Red Fish, Whiting, Pompano, Tarpon, Snapper, Wahoo, Sheepshead, Flounder, Jack, Blue Fish, Sea Trout, Black Drum, Croaker and Grouper from Cocoa Beach’s clear waters. According to Floridatoday.com, anglers are reeling-in 4–5 pound Spanish Mackerel, Ladyfish, Jack Crevalle, Redfish, and Tarpon with ease. The action should continue until Fall.</para>
    <para>When it comes to Florida fishing, Pompano are a favorite among inshore predatory fish. They’re said to possess a mild fishy taste like White Fish. “[Pompano] are one my favorite fish to catch, they put up a great fight and taste great,” said an angler. Pompano are most easily reeled-in with clam, however, anglers have had success with live bait. It’s said that Pompano bite less often than Tarpon, but the patient angler is rewarded with the region’s most beautiful catch, a shimmering blue and yellow Pompano.</para>
    <para>Tarpon are abundant along the shores of Cocoa Beach. An angler shared his fishing report: “yesterday [we] saw some major mullet pods. More importantly, we saw 4–6 foot tarpon jumping out of the water as they were nailing the bait!” The region’s Tarpon are known for aerial displays. Tarpon give a hard run before breaking the water’s surface. Upon surfacing, they are known for somersaults.</para>
    <para>Moreover, bait fish, such as Mullet, are easily pulled from Cocoa Beach’s waters. Mullet remain plentiful until October. Speaking of inshore fishing, Cocoa Beach offers some of Florida’s best pier fishing. The historic pier was constructed in 1962 by a local businessman. The pier remains an antique wooden structure that’s perfect for taking in the sun and, most importantly, casting a line. The 800-foot deck includes a bait/tackle shop, dining, and other attractions.</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Dressing Dallas’s Krishna</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para><emphasis role="underline">DISCLAIMER</emphasis>: Articles may have been published in regions where English  Creole is spoken such as India or the Ukraine. All articles are  printed as emended by the Editor. My goal is to demonstrate my ability  to write for all audiences. This includes projects for Indian and  </para>
    <para>            EasternEuropean consumers who speak their own unique blend of English  and their mother tongue. If You have a question about any particular  wording, contact me.</para>
    <para>Editorial</para>
    <para>There's an ISKCON temple in East Dallas; you may think it's a strange place for a thriving Hindu community, but it's there, 15,000 worshipers regularly gather there to get their spiritual kicks. And on Sunday, it's abuzz with gawkers and ecstatically dancing devotees.</para>
    <para>The temple came about in 1981. It was the Mount Auburn Christian Church. Devotees bought and renovated the church along with 25 homes in the neighborhood. The temple's amalgam of architecture, towers and lotus-petal-like domes were overlaid on the old church's squarish brick facade to render the typical Dallas suburb a mecca for all things Indian. It's all done well, even if just a facade on an old church. In the altar room, there's a sky blue ceiling with clouds and murals that portray Krishna frolicking with maidens, playing pranks on his mother, or dancing and charming animals with his flute in the moonlight.</para>
    <para>But we are here to discuss the idol and the cultural practices surrounding it. His name is Kalachandji, His title literally translates as the beautiful moon-faced one and He certainly looks upon the crowds with a round fat face. Devotees sing and dance along with call and response style chant and the black marble idol gazes upon His audience stoically, if you get my drift. There's a lore that surrounds this black marble statue, the idol is supposedly 500 years old, no one has ever refuted this, but I doubt it. The story goes that He was found holding the door of a showroom open in Jaipur India, bought and brought to Dallas.</para>
    <para>Dressed resplendently, Kalachandji gazes upon his audience from the altar. But, beyond the altar is a wardrobe room that hardly anyone sees. Some call it the fanciest dress shop in Texas. In this dressing room of the Gods, drawers hold elaborate garments, one for each day of the week, and hangers suspend the heavier folds of matching altar backdrops. Monday He wears red, Tuesday blue, Wednesday yellow orange, or pink, Thursday green, Friday purple. Saturday is white and Sunday He wears multi-hued garments, says Manjuali Devi Dasi, the temple president's wife, as she meditatively paces the wardrobe looking for something to dress Krishna and His Consort Radha in. She doesn't do this alone, she has the help of about 50 others, devotees known as pujaris.</para>
    <para>Kalachandji's wardrobe contains a arresting display of red, gold, pink and sea-foam green costume jewelry. It all comes from Harry Hines or India. Racks drip with necklaces, ornate necklages and shallow drawers contain bracelets, earrings, turban ornaments, toe rings and jeweled bindis that will be placed on the statues' foreheads.</para>
    <para>It's not like dolls, says Manjuali. The acts of beautification [performed here] are to please the deity, to draw the eye to the immensity of divine beauty, not for one's own pleasure or play. It's like getting the queen dressed. A few hours before dawn, the deities are awakened. A team of five devotees dresses the life-size Krishna and Radha along with their smaller attendant demigods, Gaura Nitai, Jagannatha (the eerily bug-eyed ecstatic form of Vishnu) and Radha Govinda.</para>
    <para>One devotee told DMAGAZINE that "you can't even fathom what extravagant care goes into tending the statues. The deity is bathed in milk and honey and massaged in oil. And this is merely the beginning of an elaborate set of rituals that sees them clothed and fed. The rituals are based on the Vedic idea that if these statues of black marble are treated as human, the deities will inhabit them. And so they are tended for from the 4 am wake-up call until the altar curtains close at 8:45 PM, it's like a Broadway show that never grows old to fans. At night, after he metaphorically drink a thick shake of cooked-down milk, they sleep in their pajamas.</para>
    <para>Don't expect to ever find them dressed as they were before. Every pujari has his or her own sense of style. One devotee, for example, who frequently dresses the deities on Saturday has a distinctive approach, often doing away with the halo-like effulgence and painting the deity's face with Aztec patterns. I have attended the temple many times and have seen Kalachandji adorned with Aztec-like makeup, it's arresting, just as much as the temple's ambiance tends to be: the art, the exotic call-and-response music, devotees stoned on mary-jane, those who are high on God, the constant attempts to convert any new blood.... It's all like, especially for first time attendees, entering some kind of sci-fi dream. In all, Kalachandji is made of stone, his gaze is stoic, but He's like a tractor-beam, there's something about this purportedly ancient statue that magnetic. Perhaps His charm.</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Last Splash Turns 30  But Does it Still Hold Water</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para><emphasis role="underline">DISCLAIMER</emphasis>: Articles may have been published in regions where English  Creole is spoken such as India or the Ukraine. All articles are  printed as emended by the Editor. My goal is to demonstrate my ability  to write for all audiences. This includes projects for Indian and  </para>
    <para>            EasternEuropean consumers who speak their own unique blend of English  and their mother tongue. If You have a question about any particular  wording, contact me.</para>
    <para>Editorial</para>
    <para>The Breeders' Last Splash is almost 30! I had a copy of it on cassette tape. It was one of those albums that I got lost in, I listened to it from end to end. Not just did the lyrics express my own feelings of angst and hope for tomorrow, the lo-fi sound was out of context in 1993, it was noisy, even compared to other Grunge/Alternativ  albums of the era that had a radio single. At times, Kim Deal's vocals were garbled in  layers of distortion and the guitar felt like it was being played at the end of a tunnel, while under water,  and sent through meat grinder. But, does it hold water today?</para>
    <para>The album certainly didn't die alone in the corner of a second-hand store. In 1996, the English electronic music band The Prodigy sampled a guitar ri# from S.O.S.  And, On May 13, 2013, 4AD released LSXX, a deluxe 20th anniversary edition. Most recently, Rolling Stone ranked it 293 among their revised list of the 500 Greatest Albums. There's a few effervescent pop (almost surf) rock songs like Divine Hammer and Saints on the album.</para>
    <para>I'm not using the term pop as a derogative, it's just what     they are, power chords, vocal harmonies and in your face leads prevail on these tracks.  Perhaps, it's their familiar pop and surf melodies that make these songs memorable, they surface among other noise-laden tracks like New Year and Hag. For instance, Divine Hammer is catchy as all getup and remains in my list of favorite  pop rock anthems.</para>
    <para>I never looked too deeply into the songs' lyrics; it always seemed to me like it was about wish fulfillment. After all, Thor's hammer is a giver of boons. However,  Kim Deal had this to say: "It's about existential angst, really. I'm just looking for  some divinity [to] come down [to] me here on Earth]. You could use drugs to find your divinity [or] Christian songs." I, for one, find divinity within the album, though  I wasn't aware of the meaning of these cryptic lyrics until sifting through interviews  with Deal.</para>
    <para>Adding to the odd assortment of songs, the album includes a cover of Dom Leone's  Driving on 9, a country shuffle taken out of context and reworked by Kim and the gang. Redditers seem to offer the best critique of it; they argue which HWY 9 the track refers to and whether or not the Breeders did the song justice. It's fun with violin and an underpinning of sorrow; what else can I say?</para>
    <para>And then there's the instrumentals. There's one called S.O.S (the song sampled by  The Prodigy) and another track titled Roi. I have to say, I agree with SPIN's 1993  album review on this: these tracks are pretty much indecipherable, a pastiche of smeared distortion, muted vocal musings, hills and valleys of volume and a repeated  hard rock signature. It's haunting, but [what does it all] mean? I would say nothing.  Or to elaborate, haunting for sure, but do I still want to sit through the tracks? No  These songs are like the Pixies covering Sonic Youth. Despite the creativity, this is  not a genre that warrants instrumental music.</para>
    <para>I said that some songs feel as if they were put through a meat grinder; S.O.S is just one of those tracks, Kelly Deal employed a sewing machine to get that vibrating sound. It was played through a Marshall amp. Other interesting attributes about the recording are all wave analogue production; Deal insisted that no computers, digital recording, or auto-tuning were to be used in the making of Last Splash. I get it, the Pixies purportedly recorded on 2-inch reel-to-reel. And, it's all that went into the session that makes the album feel lo-fi in the way that an abstract painting may maliciously  haphazard.</para>
    <para>I still haven't mentioned Cannonball, the album's highest-ranking single. There's  a reason for this; I don't know where to place it. As a track, I could go the rest of my life without hearing it again, it was so overplayed back in 1993, but it's a genius of a song, I know. To get the sound of that advertisement-worthy-summer-memory- inducing-hook, Kim sang the ahhhhhoooo-oooh through a harmonica mic. It's a   great sound; I just don't want to hear it again. Even the brief pause after the intro hooks the listener in.</para>
    <para>But when compared to tracks like Titled TK's Little Furry, I would call Cannonball sophomoric, oddly sophomoric for a veteran rocker like Kim Deal, after all, she  was a driving force in the Pixies. In contrast, Titled TK pushed the boundaries of pop music with sustained dissonant notes and lyrics that touch on addiction, where Last Splash, in retrospect, seems more driven by placing hit singles in a bed of oddities. In context, I would say that their first album, Pod, was more coherent and genuine. Nevertheless, I hope to turn a whole new generation onto this 4 out of 5-star album.</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">Dirty Deeds and They're Done Dirt Cheap: Ransomware</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para><emphasis role="underline">DISCLAIMER</emphasis>: Articles may have been published in regions where English  Creole is spoken such as India or the Ukraine. All articles are  printed as emended by the Editor. My goal is to demonstrate my ability  to write for all audiences. This includes projects for Indian and  </para>
    <para>            EasternEuropean consumers who speak their own unique blend of English  and their mother tongue. If You have a question about any particular  wording, contact me.</para>
    <para>Informative</para>
    <para>On average, Ransomware costs Hackers between $250 and $650. It’s hard to believe, but malicious software costs less than a used car, and this metaphorical second-hand car takes hackers further than the corner store. For their flyspeck investment, cybercriminals hijack data worth millions of dollars! In fact, bargain basement hacking software has become the norm.</para>
    <para>For instance, Stampado sells on the Dark Web for $39. Far more shocking, some commonly used hacking software is free, Kali Linux is an open-sourced operating system that provides tools for isolating weaknesses in networks, it costs nothing. Yet, Kali Linux and other such Pen Testing distributions are doled out with good intentions, unlike Stampado.</para>
    <para>All told, Stampado is no master of disguise. It’s easily detected and removed from networks. Stampado may not bring in the clams, but a modified version of it, Philadelphia Ransomware, currently sells for $389. Philadelphia Ransomware is stealthy, yet budget conscious. Worst of all, this affordable tidbit of malicious software can’t be detected by most antivirus applications. It’s a digital sniper for would-be Hackers.</para>
    <para>The Cutting Edge of Ransomware</para>
    <para>Frighteningly enough, Ransomware is constantly evolving. In fact, “developers have modified their software to offer complementary capabilities,” these modifications enable malicious software makers to provide a suite of malevolent utilities, known as Ransomware as a Service (RaaS), with no money upfront.</para>
    <para>“Ransomware 2.0,” as it was dubbed by a CISCOMag, is stealthier, sneakier, and easier than run-of-the-mill virus 1.0 for hackers to unleash on your network.</para>
    <para>If they give it away for free, how are malicious-software makers making money? Surprisingly, profit sharing is a popular business model in the shady world of Ransomware, but I guess that’s where the phrase “thick-as-thieves' originates, bandits share among themselves. In this model, Hackers divide the profits, an 80/20 split in favor of the Cybercriminal, with malware developers. This business model is referred to as Freemium or no-cost profit sharing.\</para>
    <para>Collectivism among crooks aside, Ransomware 2.0 allows Hackers to “select the targeted file extensions [or] directories, set a ransom, convert currency [between nations] and input a Bitcoin address for payment, [all] within a simple Graphical User Interface that completely eliminates the need for any coding or command line skills.” Brands, such as the aforementioned Stpedo can be found on the dark web.</para>
    <para>In the News</para>
    <para>Most recently. Ferrari was hacked by dirty rats. These rats procured and leaked 7 gigabytes of data. Among the cache were internal documents, data sheets, and repair manuals. At the time of writing this, there was little information about the exact software the hackers used, and this will probably never be divulged. Regardless of the exact method, Ransomware 1.0 or 2.0, it’s best to keep a vigilant eye out for hackers.</para>
    <para>FileAgo Puts an End to Ransomware Attacks</para>
    <para>At its’ core, Ransomware is a malignant code designed to prevent access to files, on a compromised system, until financial demands are met. These business crushing applications “leverage public key infrastructure (PKI) [and] siege autonomous offline encryption. [Worst of all these programs] are self-propagating.” But, FileAgo offers a layer of protection against Ransomware, securing your data.</para>
    <para>
      <emphasis role="bold">End Note</emphasis>
    </para>
    <para>Thanks again for reading. </para>
  </chapter>
</book>
